Guide to the Rice University Associate Provost Search records, 1985-1996 UA 049
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Associate Provost Search records
1985-1996
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University
UA 049
5.5 Linear Feet (5 boxes)
These materials include correspondence, minutes, notes, and other materials related to the searches for an Associate Provost during the years 1986, 1995, and 1996. Also included are the materials submitted by the applicants for each search. This material is restricted.
Historical Note
Rice University's Office of the Provost oversees academic, instructional, and research-related matters.
Scope and Contents
These materials include correspondence, minutes, notes, and other materials related to the Rice University Associate Provost searches conducted in 1986, 1995, and 1996. Some of the materials were created by the search committees in order to conduct the search in each year, while other materials, including resumes, references, and correspondence, were provided by the applicants of each year's search.
Access restrictions
This material is restricted. Contact Woodson Research Center staff for further information, woodson@rice.edu.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This material was acquired from the Office of the Provost in December 2006.
Index Terms
Subjects
Universities and colleges
Document Types
minutes (administrative records); letters (correspondence)
- Series I: 1986 Files, 1985-1987; 179961
  - Applicant List, 1986; 179962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Badger, George, 1986; 179973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Battin, Patricia, 1986; 179974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bender, Charles, 1986-1987; 179975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bishop, Asa Orin, 1986; 179976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bourland, Hardy M., 1986; 179977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Brereton, Stanley, 1986; 179978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Browne, James, 1986; 179979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Cade, V.S., 1986; 179980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Caret, Robert L., 1986; 179981 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Carter, Michael, 1986; 179982 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Carter, Robert L., 1986-1987; 179983 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Chance, Jane, 1986; 179984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Cherniavsky, John, 1986; 179985 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Clark, Howard D., 1986; 179986 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Coomer, J.C., 1986; 179987 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Dalphin, John F., 1986; 179988 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Daniel, James, 1986; 179989 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Davis, Clarence, 1986; 179990 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Dill, G.A., 1986; 179991 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Dinkel, John, 1986-1987; 179992 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Ecker, M.W., 1986; 179993 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Edwards, Dennis M., 1986; 179994 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Elesh, David, 1986; 179995 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Feeser, Larry, 1986-1987; 179997 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Ferguson, Richard, 1986; 179998 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Fowler, Stephen, 1986; 179999 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Gamble, John K., 1986; 180000 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Gillespie, Robert, 1986; 180001 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Gloster, Arthur S., 1986; 180002 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Gorin, Ralph E., 1986; 180003 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Gorry, G.A., 1986; 180004 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Graves, William, 1986-1987; 180005 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Hart, David A., 1986; 180006 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Hawkins, Brian, 1986; 180007 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Hays, Ronald M., 1986; 180008 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Hitt, John, 1986; 180009 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Howard, Richard D., 1986; 180010 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Hubard, Frank L., 1986; 180011 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Huston, Priscilla, 1986; 180012 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Ingle, Henry T., 1986; 180013 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Ingram, Glen, 1986; 180014 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Jennings, Dennis, 1986-1987; 180015 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Jennings, Robert R., 1986; 180016 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Johnson, Don, 1986; 180017 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Johnson, James, 1986-1987; 180018 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Karim, Raj, 1986; 180019 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Katzer, Jeffrey, 1986; 180020 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Kern, Charles W., 1986; 180021 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - King, John H., 1986; 180022 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - King, Kenneth, 1986; 180023 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Kozak, John J., 1986-1987; 180024 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Lennox, Carol, 1986; 180025 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - LeTourneau, R.H., 1986; 180026 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Lygre, John G., 1986; 180027 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Lynch, Mervin D., 1986; 180028 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Lytle, R.H., 1986; 180029 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Malak, J., 1986; 180030 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Manville, Philip Brook, 1986; 180031 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Min, L.Y., 1986; 180032 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Mittman, Ben, 1986; 180033 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Nagarajan, G., 1986; 180034 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Neibaum, Jerome, 1986; 180035 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Osterweil, Lee, 1986; 180036 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Owen, Willis L., 1986; 180037 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Panko, Walter B., 1986-1987; 180038 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Pervin, William J., 1986; 180039 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Pilcher, George W., 1986; 180040 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Pinkerton, Tad, 1986; 180041 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Rafert, Bruce, 1986; 180042 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Rahimi, Morteza, 1986-1987; 180043 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Rampp, L.C., 1986; 180044 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Resnikoff, Howard, 1986; 180045 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Ridge, George R., 1986; 180046 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Roberts, David H., 1986; 180047 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Santoro, Anthony, 1986; 180048 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Sass, Ronald, 1986; 180049 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Sellner, Ronald, 1986; 180050 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Shapiro, Martin, 1986; 180051 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Shelton, Duane, 1986; 180052 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Skarulis, Patricia, 1986; 180053 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Skolnick, Malcom, 1986; 180054 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Slater, Carl D., 1986; 180055 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Smallen, David, 1986; 180056 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Stafford, Joseph H., 1986; 180057 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Strauss, Alvin M., 1986-1987; 180058 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Stuckey, John E., 1986; 180059 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Tartar, John, 1986-1987; 180060 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Walden, William E., 1986; 180061 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Warlick, Charles, 1986; 180062 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Warren, E.H., 1986; 180063 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Weihaupt, J.G., 1986; 180064 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Wholeben, B.E., 1986; 180065 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Wiese, Theodore E., 1986; 180066 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Woodruff, Clifford, 1986; 180067 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Yarcheski, Thomas J., 1986; 180068 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Yost, Michael, 1986; 180069 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Zastrocky, Michael, 1986; 180070 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Zenger, Weldon, 1986; 180071 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Form Letters, 1986; 180083 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Job Postings, 1986; 180084 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Minutes, 1986-1987; 180085 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Neal Lane Correspondence, 1986-1987; 180086 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Neal Lane Notes, 1986-1987; 180087 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Rating Sheets, 1986; 180088 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Research Articles, 1985-1986; 180089 (Box 1, Folder 106)
- Series II: 1995 Files, 149874
  - Applicant Log, 1995; 149833 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Acevedo, Jr. Baltazar Aripse Y., 1995; 149834 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Alexion, Susan E., 1995; 149835 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bagshaw, Mark, 1995; 149836 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Baker, John, 1995; 149837 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Bazell, Dianne M., 1995; 149838 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Block, Jonathan, 1995; 149839 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Braswell, James A., 1995; 149840 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Braxton, Keylon A., 1995; 149841 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Bremer, Kristine, 1995; 149842 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Brown, Kevin L., 1995; 149843 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Burrows, Charles, 1995; 149844 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Bynum, Jack L., 1995; 149845 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Christy, Michael T., 1995; 149846 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Clark, Mark W., 1995; 149847 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Cole, Jerry L., 1995; 149848 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Colvin, Dorcas, 1995; 149849 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Condon, George A., 1995; 149850 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Condon, James M., 1995; 149851 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Cotton, Gary, 1995; 149852 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - D'annibale, Peter, 1995; 149853 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Dempsey, Ron D., 1995; 149854 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Dennard, Trudy, 1995; 149855 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - DeYoung, Gloria, 1995; 149856 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Dial, Micah, 1995; 149857 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Dilauro, Michael, 1995; 149858 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Doris, Peter A., 1995; 149859 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Durbin, Richard L., 1995; 149860 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Elsner, John A., 1995; 149861 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Ericksen, Mary, 1995; 149862 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Faries, Steve, 1995; 149863 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Fass, Leona F., 1995; 149864 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Fitts, Jean D., 1995; 149865 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Fitzgerald, Mary, 1995; 149866 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Fritz, Stephen E., 1995; 149867 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Fuller, Holly, 1995; 149868 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Gaffield, Gary, 1995; 149869 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Gardner, David W., 1995; 149870 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Gasbarra, Shane, 1995; 149871 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Gash, William, 1995; 149872 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Gerlach, Jeanne M., 1995; 149873 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Goldman, Steven, 1995; 149875 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Gorman, Vincent, 1995; 149876 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Green, Ann Herbert, 1995; 149877 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Green, Richard, 1995; 149878 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Gregory, Alexandra, 1995; 149879 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Grief, Matthew, 1995; 149880 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Grumelli, Michael, 1995; 149881 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Hall, Edward Payson, 1995; 149882 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Hall, Richard S., 1995; 149883 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Hanley, Theodore, 1995; 149884 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Harris, Edwin, 1995; 149885 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Henry, Samuel D., 1995; 149886 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Hollis, Susan T., 1995; 149887 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Holman, Fred, 1995; 149888 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Howard, Richard D., 1995; 149889 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Hugenberg, Lawrence W., 1995; 149890 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Jenkins, Karen, 1995; 149891 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Jerome, Robert T., 1995; 149892 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Jones, Dan R., 1995; 149893 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Jones, Yvette, 1995; 149894 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Julia, John B., 1995; 149895 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Kambhu, Pat, 1995; 149896 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Kelley, Ann, 1995; 149897 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Kellogg, David L., 1995; 149898 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Kleinman, Francis Susan, 1995; 149899 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Kemp, W.M., 1995; 149900 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - King, Sally Wolff, 1995; 149901 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Knock, Gary H., 1995; 149902 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Konzem, Susan, 1995; 149903 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Kunkel, Norlene M., 1995; 149904 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - La Hay, Lynette, 1995; 149905 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Laughlin, Douglas, 1995; 149906 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Lee, Robert B., 1995; 149907 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Lemura, Linda M., 1995; 149908 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Leth, Steven, 1995; 149909 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Lockey, Paul E., 1995; 149910 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Lodge, Charles, 1995; 149911 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Loper, Lori, 1995; 149912 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Loston, Adena Williams, 1995; 149913 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Madden, Ronald, 1995; 149914 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Maurer, Douglas, 1995; 149915 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - McGowan, Robert, 1995; 149916 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - McHann, James C., 1995; 149917 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - McKinney, Brian, 1995; 149918 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Medrano, Enrique, 1995; 149919 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Minar, Thomas Jackson, 1995; 149921 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Murphy, K. Thomas, 1995; 149920 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Narrett, Carla M., 1995; 149922 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Nelson, Gersham A., 1995; 149923 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Newsom, Kelly, 1995; 149924 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Nimsker, Anne R., 1995; 149925 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Nummela, Eric C., 1995; 149926 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Parate, Nath, 1995; 149927 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Patnaik, Deba, 1995; 149928 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Paulson, Joseph V., 1995; 149929 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Percy, David O., 1995; 149930 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Prater, Barbara, 1995; 149931 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Perry, D. Gaye Bumsted, 149932 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Ponder, Fred T., 1995; 149933 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Poux, Claude Joseph, 1995; 149934 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Pursely, Evelyn M., 1995; 149935 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Purtee, Debra, 1995; 149936 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Rader, Bill, 1995; 149937 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Ralph, Michael, 1995; 149938 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Ranu, H.S., 1995; 149939 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Reid, James A., 1995; 149940 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Renner, Sonya L., 1995; 149941 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Rice, Stephen, 1995; 149942 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Richards, C. Steven, 1995; 149943 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Rodas, Daniel J., 1995; 149944 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Ross, Jacqueline, 1995; 149945 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Ruffolo, John, 1995; 149946 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Schaaf, Judy, 1995; 149947 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Schaffer, Dennis R., 1995; 149948 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Schou, Gayle E., 1995; 149949 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Scott, Naomi, 1995; 149950 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Seymour, Daniel T., 1995; 149951 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Shatzman, Aaron, 1995; 149952 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Shillingsburg, Miriam, 1995; 149953 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Sleight, Richard G., 1995; 149954 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Slinker, Michael J., 1995; 149955 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Strong, Susan, 1995; 149956 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Sullivan, Michael L., 1995; 149957 (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Tannahill, Neal, 1995; 149958 (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Taylor, David, 1995; 149959 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Tezak, Edward, 1995; 149960 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Thomas, Anthony M., 1995; 149961 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Trachtenberg, Stanley, 1995; 149962 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Trybul, Theodore, 1995; 149963 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Turk, Suzanne, 1995; 149964 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - Turner, Larry W., 1995; 149965 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Tyler, Matthew, 1995; 149966 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Viebig, Judy G., 1995; 149967 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Williams, Lois, 1995; 149968 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Wisener, Don, 1995; 149969 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Wolcowitz, Jeffery, 1995; 149970 (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - Zeplin, Gary, 1995; 149971 (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Zhang, Jiuwu (Mark), 1995; 149972 (Box 2, Folder 139)
- Series III: 1996 Files, 1993-1996; 149973
  - Adams, Elaine P., 1996; 150058 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Alexander, Charles J., 1996; 150060 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Alexander, Charles - Travel, 1996; 150059 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Arnold, Jasper H., 1996; 150061 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Ayers, Kenya, 1996; 150062 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Birdine, Steven T., 1995-1996; 150057 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Blell, Denys Santos, 1996; 150053 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Blell, Denys - Travel, 1996; 150054 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Bradley, Odra W., 1996; 150055 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Brady, Thomas E., 1996; 150056 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Broussard, Nan, 1996; 149974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Brown-Long, Rosita, 1996; 149975 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Carolina, Demetrius, 1996; 149976 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Collins, Vanneisa A., 1996; 149977 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Contee, Jerome A., 1996; 149978 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Copeland, Jim, 1996; 149980 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Davis, Daniel C., 1996; 149981 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Davis, Donn G., 1996; 149982 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - de Necochea, Fernando, 1996; 150029 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - de Necochea, Fernando - Travel, 1996; 150028 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Dennard, Trudy Cobb, 1996; 149983 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Duncan, Edgar N., 1996; 150030 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Fain, Nancy C., 1996; 150031 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Farmer, Shanan W., 1996; 150032 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Friday, Yvonne W., 1996; 150033 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Ganopole, Selina J., 1996; 150034 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Garfield, Jane, 1996; 150035 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Geter, Leroy, 1996; 150036 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Giardino, John R., 1996; 150037 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Gillis, Robert E., 1996; 150038 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Goin, Ruth, 1996; 150039 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Gomez, Gerard, 1996; 150040 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Hagedorn, Geneva D., 1996; 150041 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Hawkins, Fanny, 1996; 150042 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Heggie, James A., 1996; 150043 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Hein, Warren W., 1996; 150044 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Hsu, Laura Ling, 1996; 150090 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Ibarra, Robert A., 1996; 150046 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Ibarra, Robert - Travel, 1996; 150045 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Jackson, George A., 1996; 150047 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Jarvis, Robert L., 1996; 150048 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Jolly, Samone Louise, 1996; 150049 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Kaurouma, Patricia, 1996; 150051 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Kenkel, Norlene, 1996; 149984 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Kent, Margaret, 1996; 149985 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Key, Bonnie B., 1996; 149986 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - King, Deborah E., 1996; 149987 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - King, Joe, 1996; 149988 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Klein, Bernard, 1996; 149989 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Krajewski, Robert J., 1996; 149990 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Leal-Quiros, Edbertho, 1996; 149991 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Lee, Maurice, 1996; 149992 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Liddell, Ben, 1996; 149993 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Lopez, Omar S., 1996; 149994 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Martin-Terry, Wanda J., 1996; 149995 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Matthews Jr., Graham P., 1996; 149996 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - McClure, Jesse F., 1996; 149997 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Medrano, Enrique, 1996; 149998 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Middleton, Earnest, 1996; 149999 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Morrison, K.C., 1995-1996; 150102 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Nagai, Tsuneo, 1996; 150000 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Neri, Jerry, 1996; 150001 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Oliver, Bernard, 1996; 150002 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Pardue, Robert L., 1996; 150003 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Patterson, G. Dean, 1996; 150004 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Peterson, Sylvester L., 1996; 150005 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Proctor, Maxine, 1996; 150006 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Pullian, Roger L., 1996; 150007 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Ramirez, Ronaldo, 1996; 150008 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Reid, Sue T., 1996; 150009 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Robinson, Marchris G., 1996; 150010 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Roche, Patrick, 1995-1996; 150011 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Russell, Joseph, 1996; 150063 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Saavedra, Rebecca, 1995-1996; 150064 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Saffari, Mahmoud, 1995-1996; 150065 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Santamaria, Philip, 1995-1996; 150066 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Santiago, Emily, 1995-1996; 150067 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Scott, Stanley V., 1996; 150069 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Simmons, Ron, 1995-1996; 150070 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Soliz, Rudy, 1996; 150072 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Taylor-Archer, Mordean, 1996; 150075 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Taylor-Archer, Mordean - Travel, 1996; 150076 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Torres, Antoinette, 1995-1996; 150103 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Torres, David A., 1995-1996; 150077 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Tu Dutka, Julia, 1996; 150078 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Uscher, Nancy J., 1996; 150079 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Vickers, Joanne F., 1995-1996; 150080 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Walters, Evan, 1996; 150081 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Watson, Earnest Jr., 1995-1996; 150082 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Webster, Otis S., 1995-1996; 150083 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Williams, Diane L., 1996; 150084 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Williams, RIchard A., 1996; 150085 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Advertisements, 1995-1996; 150091 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Associate Provost Candidates, 1993-1994; 150104 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Associate Provost Candidates, 1995; n.d.; 180090 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Associate Provost Search, n.d.; 150105 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Candidate Master List, 1996; 150086 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Charge Letter, 1995; 150095 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Committee Expenses, 1996; 150100 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Completed Ranking Forms, n.d.; 150087 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Finalist Listings - Voting and No Votes, February 1996; 150089 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - General Correspondence, 1995-1996; n.d.; 150094 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Job Description, n.d.; 150101 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Meeting Notices, 1995; 150097 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Nominations, 1995-1996; 150098 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Persons Solicited, 1996; 150099 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Rejection Letters, 1996; 180091 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Sample Information, 1996; 150096 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Search Committee, 1995; 150092 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Search Committee List, 1995-1996; 150093 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Voting Forms for Finalists, n.d.; 150088 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Series IV: Oversize Materials, 1986-1996; 179967
  - Advertisements, 1995; 180077 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Bender, Charles, 180079 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Birdine, Steven T., 1995; 180072 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Carter, Michael, n.d.; 180081 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Hsu, Laura Ling, 1994-1996; 180078 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - King, Joe, 1994, n.d.; 180073 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Lee, Maurice, 1994; 180074 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - LeTourneau, R.H., n.d.; 180080 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Morrison, K.C., 1994; 180076 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Research Articles, 1985-1986; 180082 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Soliz, Rudy, 1993; 180075 (Box 5, Folder 11)